<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ATINs NLC</string>
    <string name="news_description">Be the first to know about crucial updates, deadlines, and important announcements directly from the college administration. We believe in transparent communication, and this section ensures you have access to all the information you need to succeed.

Atin NLC Mandra is more than just a place of education its a thriving community with a pulse that beats with the energy of its members. Dive into the "News and Events" section to experience the heartbeat of our college and stay connected to the pulse of the latest news and exciting events.

Stay tuned for whats next, and let the journey of discovery and celebration begin.</string>
    <string name="fee_structure">
        Welcome to the Fee Structure section of Applied Technologies Institutes NLC Mandra. We understand the importance of transparent and accessible information regarding fees for our students. Below, you will find a detailed breakdown of the various fees associated with our programs.
    </string>

    <string name="course_catalog_desc">Welcome to our esteemed technical institute offering a comprehensive Diploma of Associate Engineering (DAE) program with a focus on shaping future leaders in various engineering disciplines. Our three-year program is designed to provide students with a solid foundation in technical knowledge, practical skills, and industry-relevant expertise.</string>

    <string name="IOTAT">Explore the cutting-edge world of the Internet of Things (IoT) and Automation Technology. This program equips students with the skills to design, implement, and manage interconnected devices, enabling them to contribute to the rapidly evolving field of smart technologies.</string>
    <string name="MMAT">Delve into the realm of Mechanical Engineering, Manufacturing, and Automation Technology. This specialization covers the principles of machinery, manufacturing processes, and automation techniques, preparing students for diverse roles in the mechanical and manufacturing industries.</string>
    <string name="CIT">Embark on a journey into the dynamic field of Computer Information Technology. This program focuses on computer systems, networks, software development, and data management, empowering students to excel in the ever-evolving landscape of information technology.</string>
    <string name="CIVIL">Build a strong foundation in Civil Engineering, where students learn the principles of construction, infrastructure development, and project management. Graduates are prepared to contribute to the planning and execution of civil engineering projects.</string>
    <string name="MECH">Gain expertise in Mechanical Engineering, covering a broad spectrum of topics such as thermodynamics, fluid mechanics, and machine design. This program prepares students for roles in the design, analysis, and maintenance of mechanical systems.</string>
    <string name="about_us1">is located on Grand Trunk Road Mandra about 40 Kms from Rawalpindi at outskirts of Rawalpindi Division. The institute was established in Nov 2006 over 27 Acres land. It is one of the leading Technical and Vocational Training Institute and is one of the few with courses/ programs in Heavy Machinery Op- erator/Mechanical Handling Equiment and is immensely contribut- ing in nation building by imparting skills the youths of Pakistan. The training methodology revolves around the basic objective of provid- ing hands-on skills to un-employed, under-educated and venera- ble youth of society. The institute is accredited with National Voca- tional and Technical Training Commission (NAVTTC) Islamabad, National Training Bureau (NTB) Islamabad, Technical Education and Vocational Training Authority (TEVTA) Punjab, Punjab Board of Technical Education (PBTE) and is ISO 9001: 2015 certified.\n\n</string>
    <string name="about_us3">\nThe institute currently has a capacity to train over 150 trainees per session, with in house boarding and lodging facilities for over 150 students. The Institute with expe- rienced faculty of engineers, field instructors having de- cades of experience with sufficient training equipment and infrastructure to meet all training and administrative requirements</string>
    <string name="about_us2">3 Years Program - Diploma of Associate Engineer (DAE).\n1.DAE Civil\n2.DAE Mechanical\n3.DAE Computer Information Technology (CIT).\n</string>
</resources>